[{"question": " i hate this apartment! i hate the color of these walls! i hate the fact that this place still smells like bird! i hate that singing guy!", "answer": " are you kidding? i love that guy!  morning\u0092s here! morning is here\u0097", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " stop it! i will kill you. i hate the fact that my room is so small.", "answer": " hey, i have all the space i need. just do what i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " monica, you don\u0092t even have a bed, you sleep in a ball on the floor!", "answer": " y\u0092know what? i am really tired of your bellyaching! okay, i-i worked really hard at making this a nice place for us to live!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry. i\u0092m so sorry.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " see, this is a great apartment.", "answer": " shut up! this place is a hole! opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " he does that?!", "answer": " uh, i don\u0092t know, whatever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " i think it makes you look really dangerous.", "answer": " oh, i know. y\u0092know what, i never would\u0092ve gotten this if it weren\u0092t for you. no really, when i\u0092m with you i\u0092m-i\u0092m like this whole other guy, i love that guy! i mean, i love you too, a lot, but that guy! i-i love that guy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " i love both of you!", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " i wish i didn\u0092t have to go.", "answer": " then don\u0092t. stay here. just don\u0092t go so soon to london, just one more day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " ohh, ross, please!", "answer": " one more day, seriously/", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " don\u0092t do this to me, again. you\u0092d know i\u0092d stay here in a minute, but i\u0092d really miss so much work, they\u0092ll fire me.", "answer": " so, then you can stay as long as you want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i wish i could.", "answer": " oh no. don\u0092t, don\u0092t, don\u0092t start packing. come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " i don\u0092t think you understand packing. look, i just don\u0092t want to leave it to the last minute. last time i left in such a rush, i left my knickers here.", "answer": " yeah, i know, i uh, i tried them on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " you didn\u0092t!", "answer": " no. no, i didn\u0092t. i didn\u0092t want to be that guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  hello!", "answer": " ho! ho! ho!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " excuse me.", "answer": " your pants!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh, yeah! you like \u0091em? i just, i went to a used clothes store and got a bunch of maternity stuff. these are sooo comfortable!", "answer": " uhh, pheebs, those are uh, those are santa pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " santa pants.  santa claus\u0092s pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " nuh-uh! they\u0092re maternity pants. they even came with a list of baby names.  see, these names are good, and these names are bad.  ohh.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " so\u0097hey, pheebs! so, how are the elves?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know! how are the-the-the-the, y\u0092know\u0097you\u0092re clothes aren\u0092t funny.", "answer": " hey, guys, what-what should i wear to a knicks game?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " uhh, a t-shirt that says, \"i don\u0092t belong here.\"", "answer": " you have knicks tickets?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " yeah, my mom got my dad\u0092s season tickets in the divorce, so she just gave them to me.", "answer": " yeah, apparently, they\u0092re pretty good seats.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": "  oh my god! those are almost right on the floor!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " do you guys want these?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " yeah we do!", "answer": " ohh, well you got \u0091em.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " all right!", "answer": " just give us our apartment back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " boy! i didn\u0092t see that coming!", "answer": " are you serious?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh, come on! we know what these are worth.", "answer": " yeah, what, do you think we\u0092re stupid?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " you\u0092re not stupid. you\u0092re meaner than i thought.", "answer": " what do you say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " forget it! okay, i\u0092m not giving up my bachelor pad for some basketball seats!", "answer": " you\u0092re bachelor pad?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " have you even had a girl up here?", "answer": " no. but uh, joey has, and i usually talk to them in the morning time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " come on!", "answer": "  yes, gunther, can i get two cups of chino, please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " good one.", "answer": " come on, season tickets! season tickets, do you know what that means?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " forget it! okay, i\u0092m not giving up the apartment.", "answer": " oh come\u0097look, when i was a kid my dad\u0092s company gave season tickets to the number one salesman every year, all right? my dad never won! of course, he wasn\u0092t in the sales division, but still, i never ever, ever forgot that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " we don\u0092t make enough fun of you already?", "answer": " oh yeah, emily convinced me to do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " you do know that wham broke up?", "answer": " i like it, and emily likes it, and that\u0092s what counts. so uh, how are you guys doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh-no, don\u0092t try and talk all normal with that thing in your ear.", "answer": " where is emily?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " ugh, she\u0092s saying good-bye to her uncle.", "answer": " man, didn\u0092t she like just get here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " yeah!! yeah!", "answer": " easy tiger.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " i just, i hate this so much! i mean, every time i go pick her up at the airport, it\u0092s-it\u0092s so great. but at the same time i\u0092m thinking, \"well, i\u0092m gonna be right back there in a couple of days, dropping her off.\"", "answer": " so what are you going to do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " nothing! there\u0092s nothing to do! i mean, she lives there, i live here. i mean, she-she\u0092d have to uh, move here. she should move here!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i could ask her to live with me!", "answer": " are you serious?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " i mean, why not! i mean, i mean why not?!", "answer": " because you\u0092ve only known her for six weeks! okay, i\u0092ve got a carton of milk in my fridge i\u0092ve had a longer relationship with!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " look guys, when i\u0092m with her it\u0092s-it\u0092s-it\u0092s like she brings this-this-this great side out of me. i mean i-i-i love her, y\u0092know?", "answer": " and i love the milk! but, i\u0092m not gonna some british girl to move in with me!  joey, you say things now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " all right look, ross, he\u0092s right. emily\u0092s great, she\u0092s great! but this way too soon, you\u0092re only gonna scare her!", "answer": " i don\u0092t want to do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " no! you don\u0092t want to wreck it, you don\u0092t want to go to fast!", "answer": " yeah, no, you\u0092re right, i know, you\u0092re right, i\u0092m not, i\u0092m not gonna do it. all right, thanks guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " that\u0092s too hard. too hard!", "answer": "  all right boys, last chance for the tickets!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " or i\u0092ll give them to my new boyfriend, joshua.", "answer": " no thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " wait-wait-wait-wait!  come on! come on, let\u0092s trade! the timing\u0092s perfect, i just clogged the toilet!", "answer": " look, i want those basketball seats as much as you do! okay, but we can\u0092t leave in the small apartment after we\u0092ve lived here! didn\u0092t you ever read flowers for algernon?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " yes! didn\u0092t you ever read sports illustrated?! no! i didn\u0092t read yours! but come on, we can go to the game tonight!", "answer": " look, the only way i will even consider this is if they offer a lot more than just season seats.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " it\u0092s the knicks!", "answer": " screw the knicks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " whoa!", "answer": " i didn\u0092t mean that. i just meant that the apartment is worth so much more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " huh.", "answer": " and the knicks rule all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah, the knicks rule all!", "answer": " hey, so? are you gonna do it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " no. no. we\u0092re not gonna do that, y\u0092know why? because its not an even trade.", "answer": " all right, okay, look, what if you could keep the apartment and get the tickets?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " done!", "answer": " let me finish.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " i\u0092m talking about a bet, winner takes all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " ooh, we could end up with nothing.", "answer": " or you could end up with everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " ooh, i like that.", "answer": " all right, so what do you say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " oh, just do it!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " op, op, i\u0092m convinced!", "answer": " come on man, you know i\u0092d do it for you! because, you\u0092re my best friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " all right, but you can\u0092t use that again for a whole year. i\u0092m in.", "answer": " all right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " ooh, this is so exciting! ooh, god, what are you going to bet?", "answer": " oh, okay, well, i think we should let phoebe decide, because she\u0092s the only who\u0092s impartial, and she\u0092s so pretty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " okay. umm, ooh, ooh\u0097oh, i have a game!", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " this is great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " what\u0092s the game?! what\u0092s the game?!", "answer": " oh, well, it doesn\u0092t have a name\u0097oh, okay, phoebeball! no, it doesn\u0092t have a name. umm, okay, monica, what is your favourite thing about trees?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " they\u0092re green?", "answer": " good! good! five points!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " uhh, they\u0092re tall.", "answer": " ooh, three points. both fine answers, but we were looking for leafy, leafy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " that\u0092s not even a game!", "answer": " what? shut up! we\u0092re winning!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " you wanna finish this right now? all right, we get a deck of cards, high card wins. what do you say?", "answer": " fine, let\u0092s do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh, i have cards!", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh, good.", "answer": " yeah! here!  oh no, these are the trick deck. okay. here yes. okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " okay, you guys uh, you guys pick first", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " okay.  four.", "answer": " that\u0092s a low one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " yeah! okay.  phoebe, you look, i can\u0092t.", "answer": " what make you think i can?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " why are you screaming and hugging?", "answer": " because we won our apartment back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " what? ace is high! jack, queen, king, ace!", "answer": " no! ace is low! ace, two, three, four!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know. ooh! ooh! look it!  ah-ha!", "answer": " all right, cut, let\u0092s pick again, pick again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " come on apartment! come on apartment!  oh! i know queen is high!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " uh-huh, not as high as\u009a it worked! king!", "answer": " yeah baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " but, we pick again! we pick again!", "answer": " why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know!", "answer": " tickets please!  that\u0092s courtside baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " seriously, good game though. good game.   what are they so mad about? they get the apartment back!", "answer": " no they didn\u0092t!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " i packed while you were gone. i left some knickers under your pillow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  move in with me.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " don\u0092t be scared, i-i know it sounds crazy and-and people will say it\u0092s too soon, but just-just think, think how great it will be.", "answer": " ohh, no. ugh. oh, leaving london, my whole family lives there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " my job!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " well, so, you-you\u0092ll get a job here! i mean, i\u0092m always hearing about uh, them foreigners coming in here and stealing american jobs; that could be you!", "answer": " yeah, but it-it-it\u0092s my whole life\u0097you come to england.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no, i can\u0092t. i would, i really would, but my son is here; i can\u0092t leave him. isn\u0092t\u0097you don\u0092t think there\u0092s any way?", "answer": " ohh, i don\u0092t think so. i mean it would be different if it was way into the future \u0096and-and-and we were getting married or something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " oh no, no, right i shouldn\u0092t have said married. uh, please don\u0092t go freaky on me. i didn\u0092t mean it. well, i didn\u0092t say it; i take it back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " no, no, don\u0092t. why don\u0092t we?", "answer": " why don\u0092t we what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " get married.", "answer": " you are mad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " no! no! i\u0092m not! it\u0092s-it\u0092s-it\u0092s perfect! i mean it\u0092s better than you just-just moving here, \u0091cause it\u0092s us together forever, and that\u0092s-that\u0092s what i want.", "answer": " we\u0092ve only known each other for six weeks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " yeah, i know, so what? i mean, who\u0092s-who\u0092s to say? does that me we-we can\u0092t do it? look, huh, i was with carol for four years before we got married and i wound up divorced from a pregnant lesbian. i mean, this, this makes sense for us. come on! i mean, on our first date we ended up spending the whole weekend in vermont! i mean, last night i got my ear pierced! me! this feels right. doesn\u0092t it?", "answer": " my parents are going to be really mad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " is that\u0097are you saying yes? is that yes?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " yes! we\u0092re getting married?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " we\u0092re getting married!", "answer": " come here, come here. uh,  ow! emily, will you marry me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " ohh, it\u0092s a bit small.", "answer": " damn! i thought that was going to be romantic as hell!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " those were like the best seats ever.", "answer": " oh yeah. hey! should we give these shirts to the girls? y\u0092know, kinda like a peace offering.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " hey, want a beer?   whoa!!!!", "answer": " i know!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " we are switching back, right now!", "answer": " no, we\u0092re not! we\u0092re not leaving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " well, you\u0092re gonna have to leave sometime, because you both have jobs, and as soon as you do, we\u0092re switching it back! there\u0092s nothing you can do to stop us! right, joe?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i don\u0092t want to move again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " all right. we figured you might respond this way, so we have a backup offer.", "answer": " oh no-no-no, no more offers. you can\u0092t offer anything to us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " let us keep the apartment and\u009a", "answer": " as a thank you, rachel and i will kiss for one minute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " totally worth it!", "answer": " that was one good minute!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " good night.", "answer": " good night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " men are such idiots.", "answer": " yeah! can you believe that something that stupid actually got us our apartment back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " that\u0092s so funny to think if you\u0092d just done that right after the last contest, no one would have had to move at all.", "answer": " yeah, let-let-let\u0092s pretend that\u0092s not true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " okay, scarf\u0092s done.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " come on! come on. come on.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " what-what\u0092s going on?", "answer": " ross has some big thing to tell everyone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " what? oh, are you pregnant too?!", "answer": " umm, no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " when, when did\u0097how, how did you\u009a", "answer": " we, we just decided to uh, to go for it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": "  umm, uh, i was just telling the guys\u009a", "answer": " yeah, i-i heard.  i think it\u0092s great!  ohh, i\u0092m so happy for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " oh, well, that\u0092s great!", "answer": " yeah! yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": "  i can\u0092t believe you\u0092re getting married!", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " monica and rachel made out.  closing credits", "answer": "  morning\u0092s here! the morning\u0092s here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " sunshine is here! the sky is clear, the morning\u0092s here! the singing man: hey! you\u0092re back!", "answer": " hey!  get into gear! the singing man:  breakfast is near!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " the dark of night has disappeared!! the singing man: i\u0092ll see you tomorrow morning!", "answer": "  okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}]